<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monk Fitness</string>
    <string name="week_label">Week %d</string>
    <string name="today_workout">TODAY\'S WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="completed">completed</string>
    <string name="progress_percent">%1$d%% completed</string>
    <string name="streak">Streak</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="day_display">Day %1$d</string>
    <string name="day_format">%1$d/56</string>
    <string name="start_workout">Start Workout</string>
    <string name="complete_workout">Complete Workout</string>
    <string name="label_description">Description</string>
    <string name="label_steps">How to perform</string>
    <string name="label_technique">Technique</string>
    <string name="label_mistakes">Common mistakes</string>
    <string name="description">Content loading error.</string>
    <string name="steps_default">Content loading error.</string>
    <string name="technique">Content loading error.</string>
    <string name="mistakes_default">Content loading error.</string>
    <string name="your_progress">Your Progress</string>
    <string name="no_progress_yet">Start your first workout to see your progress chart!</string>
    <string name="completed_days">Total Completed Days: %d</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="set_notification_time">Set Daily Reminder Time</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="timer_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="timer_start">Start</string>
    <string name="timer_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="rest">Rest</string>
    <string name="skip_rest">Skip Rest</string>
    <string name="next_label">Next: %s</string>
    <string name="steps">How to perform</string>
    <string name="mistakes">Common mistakes</string>
    <string name="warmup">Warmup</string>
    <string name="warmup_desc">Prepare your body for the main workout.</string>
    <string name="main_workout">Main Workout</string>
    <string name="posture_block">Posture Block</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="workout_complete">Workout Complete!</string>
    <string name="workout_complete_desc">Great job! You have completed today\'s session.</string>
    <string name="rest_day">Rest Day</string>
    <string name="rest_day_message">Recovery, walking, light mobility. Give your muscles time to grow.</string>
    <string name="vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="timer_ticks">Timer Ticks</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="lang_en">English</string>
    <string name="lang_ru">Russian</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="posture">Posture</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_name">Daily Reminder</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Time to Workout!</string>
    <string name="notification_text">Keep your streak alive. Start your daily workout now.</string>
    <string name="posture_training">Posture Training</string>
    <string name="posture_desc">Correct your posture with these daily exercises.</string>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <string name="cat_strength">Strength</string>
    <string name="cat_mobility">Mobility</string>
    <string name="cat_stretching">Stretching</string>
    <string name="cat_posture">Posture</string>
    <string name="subcat_shoulders">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="subcat_spine">Spine</string>
    <string name="subcat_hips">Hips</string>
    <string name="subcat_legs">Legs</string>
    <string name="subcat_core">Core</string>
    <string name="subcat_fullbody">Full Body</string>
    <string name="filter_all">All</string>

    <!-- Onboarding -->
    <string name="onboarding_title">Welcome to Monk Fitness</string>
    <string name="onboarding_desc">Embark on a structured 8-week program designed to transform your strength and mobility. Follow daily workouts, track your progress, and stay consistent with our streak system.</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>

    <!-- Exercises -->
    <string name="ex_pushups">Pushups</string>
    <string name="ex_pushups_desc">A fundamental upper body exercise that strengthens the chest, shoulders, and triceps while engaging the core.</string>
    <string name="ex_pushups_steps">1. Start in a high plank position with hands slightly wider than shoulders.\n2. Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor.\n3. Keep your body in a straight line from head to heels.\n4. Push yourself back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_pushups_tech">Keep elbows at a 45-degree angle to your torso. Engage your glutes and core to maintain a rigid body line. Focus on a full range of motion.</string>
    <string name="ex_pushups_mistakes">Sagging hips, flared elbows (90 degrees), looking up instead of keeping neck neutral, and restricted range of motion.</string>

    <string name="ex_squats">Squats</string>
    <string name="ex_squats_desc">A powerful compound exercise that targets the quadriceps, hamstrings, and glutes.</string>
    <string name="ex_squats_steps">1. Stand with feet shoulder-width apart, toes slightly pointed out.\n2. Inhale and lower your hips by bending knees as if sitting in a chair.\n3. Go down until thighs are parallel to the floor or lower.\n4. Exhale and drive through your heels to return to a standing position.</string>
    <string name="ex_squats_tech">Keep your chest up and back flat. Your knees should track in line with your toes. Distribute weight evenly on your heels and mid-foot.</string>
    <string name="ex_squats_mistakes">Knees caving inward, heels lifting off the floor, rounding the lower back, and not going deep enough.</string>

    <string name="ex_pullups">Pullups</string>
    <string name="ex_pullups_desc">The ultimate bodyweight back exercise, focusing on the latissimus dorsi, biceps, and grip strength.</string>
    <string name="ex_pullups_steps">1. Grab the bar with an overhand grip, slightly wider than shoulder-width.\n2. Start from a dead hang with arms fully extended.\n3. Pull your body up by driving elbows down until your chin is over the bar.\n4. Lower yourself back down with control to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_pullups_tech">Engage your shoulder blades by pulling them down and back before you start the pull. Avoid using momentum or swinging your legs (kipping).</string>
    <string name="ex_pullups_mistakes">Using momentum/swinging, not reaching full extension at the bottom, and shrugging shoulders toward ears.</string>

    <string name="ex_plank">Plank</string>
    <string name="ex_plank_desc">A core stability exercise that builds isometric strength throughout the entire trunk.</string>
    <string name="ex_plank_steps">1. Place forearms on the floor, elbows directly under shoulders.\n2. Extend legs behind you, resting weight on toes.\n3. Form a straight line from head to heels.\n4. Hold the position while breathing deeply and maintaining tension.</string>
    <string name="ex_plank_tech">Squeeze your glutes and quadriceps to stabilize the pelvis. Push away from the floor through your forearms to engage the serratus anterior.</string>
    <string name="ex_plank_mistakes">Sagging hips, lifting the glutes too high (peaking), holding breath, and looking forward rather than down.</string>

    <string name="ex_dips">Dips</string>
    <string name="ex_dips_desc">An effective exercise for isolating the triceps and building lower chest strength.</string>
    <string name="ex_dips_steps">1. Grip parallel bars and lift yourself up with locked arms.\n2. Lower your body by bending elbows until they are at a 90-degree angle.\n3. Keep your torso slightly leaned forward for chest emphasis or upright for triceps.\n4. Push back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_dips_tech">Keep your shoulders down and away from your ears. Ensure elbows don\'t flare out too much. Control the descent to protect the shoulder joint.</string>
    <string name="ex_dips_mistakes">Flaring elbows, excessive swinging, and dipping too deep (below 90 degrees) which can strain shoulders.</string>

    <string name="ex_lunges">Lunges</string>
    <string name="ex_lunges_desc">A functional lower body movement that improves balance, coordination, and leg strength.</string>
    <string name="ex_lunges_steps">1. Stand tall and take a large step forward with one leg.\n2. Lower your hips until both knees are bent at approximately 90 degrees.\n3. Your back knee should hover just above the floor.\n4. Push off the front foot to return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_lunges_tech">Keep your torso upright and core engaged. Ensure the front knee stays aligned with the foot and doesn\'t collapse inward.</string>
    <string name="ex_lunges_mistakes">Leaning too far forward, front knee passing the toes, and losing balance due to a narrow stance.</string>

    <string name="ex_rows">Rows</string>
    <string name="ex_rows_desc">A pull exercise that builds thickness in the upper and middle back.</string>
    <string name="ex_rows_steps">1. Hinge at the hips with a flat back, holding a weight or resistance band.\n2. Pull the weight toward your lower ribs, squeezing shoulder blades together.\n3. Hold for a second at the top of the movement.\n4. Slowly lower the weight back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_rows_tech">Keep your spine neutral throughout. Focus on pulling with your elbows rather than your hands. Do not use your lower back to swing the weight.</string>
    <string name="ex_rows_mistakes">Rounding the back, using momentum, and not reaching a full range of motion.</string>

    <string name="ex_leg_raises">Leg Raises</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_raises_desc">An abdominal exercise that specifically targets the lower portion of the rectus abdominis.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_raises_steps">1. Lie flat on your back with legs straight and hands by your sides or under your glutes.\n2. Lift your legs toward the ceiling until they are at a 90-degree angle.\n3. Slowly lower your legs back down without letting them touch the floor.\n4. Keep your lower back pressed firmly into the ground.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_raises_tech">Exhale as you lift and inhale as you lower. If your back arches, don\'t lower your legs as far. Focus on the tension in your lower abs.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_raises_mistakes">Arching the lower back, lifting legs with momentum, and bending the knees.</string>

    <string name="ex_cat_cow">Cat Cow</string>
    <string name="ex_cat_cow_desc">A gentle flow that improves spinal mobility and coordinates movement with breath.</string>
    <string name="ex_cat_cow_steps">1. Start on all fours with wrists under shoulders and knees under hips.\n2. Inhale: Drop your belly, lift your chest and tailbone (Cow).\n3. Exhale: Round your back, tuck your chin and tailbone (Cat).\n4. Repeat the flow smoothly with your breath.</string>
    <string name="ex_cat_cow_tech">Move slowly and feel each vertebra. Keep your arms straight throughout the entire movement. Focus on the transition between the two poses.</string>
    <string name="ex_cat_cow_mistakes">Moving too fast, bending the elbows, and forcing the range of motion.</string>

    <string name="ex_bird_dog">Bird Dog</string>
    <string name="ex_bird_dog_desc">A core exercise that emphasizes stability, balance, and coordination between the upper and lower body.</string>
    <string name="ex_bird_dog_steps">1. Start on all fours in a neutral spine position.\n2. Simultaneously extend your right arm forward and left leg backward.\n3. Hold for 2 seconds while maintaining a flat back.\n4. Return to the starting position and switch sides.</string>
    <string name="ex_bird_dog_tech">Keep your hips and shoulders square to the floor. Imagine a glass of water on your back that you shouldn\'t spill. Do not lift your leg higher than hip level.</string>
    <string name="ex_bird_dog_mistakes">Arching the back, lifting the leg too high, and rotating the hips.</string>

    <string name="ex_stretch">World\'s Greatest Stretch</string>
    <string name="ex_stretch_desc">A comprehensive mobility drill that opens up the hips, thoracic spine, and hamstrings.</string>
    <string name="ex_stretch_steps">1. Step forward into a deep lunge.\n2. Place the inside elbow to the instep of the front foot.\n3. Rotate the same-side arm toward the ceiling, following with your eyes.\n4. Return and step back, then switch sides.</string>
    <string name="ex_stretch_tech">Take your time in each position. Breathe deeply. Keep the back leg straight and active to maximize the hip flexor stretch.</string>
    <string name="ex_stretch_mistakes">Rushing through the movements and not reaching for full rotation.</string>

    <string name="ex_burpees">Burpees</string>
    <string name="ex_burpees_desc">A high-intensity, full-body exercise for conditioning and explosive power.</string>
    <string name="ex_burpees_steps">1. From a standing position, drop into a squat and place hands on the floor.\n2. Kick your feet back into a plank and perform a push-up.\n3. Jump your feet back toward your hands.\n4. Explode upward into a jump with hands overhead.</string>
    <string name="ex_burpees_tech">Maintain a steady pace. Keep your core tight during the plank and push-up phases. Land softly on your feet after the jump.</string>
    <string name="ex_burpees_mistakes">Sagging hips during the push-up, landing flat-footed, and skipping the full range of motion.</string>

    <string name="ex_climbers">Mountain Climbers</string>
    <string name="ex_climbers_desc">A dynamic plank variation that challenges core stability while providing a cardiovascular stimulus.</string>
    <string name="ex_climbers_steps">1. Start in a high plank position.\n2. Drive one knee toward your chest, then quickly switch legs.\n3. Continue the "running" motion while keeping your hips stable.\n4. Maintain a flat back throughout the exercise.</string>
    <string name="ex_climbers_tech">Keep your shoulders directly over your wrists. Minimize hip bounce. Focus on the "crunch" as the knee comes toward the chest.</string>
    <string name="ex_climbers_mistakes">Bouncing the hips, weight shifting too far back, and not bringing knees far enough forward.</string>

    <string name="ex_kb_swing">Kettlebell Swing</string>
    <string name="ex_kb_swing_desc">An explosive hip-hinge movement that builds power in the posterior chain.</string>
    <string name="ex_kb_swing_steps">1. Stand with feet wider than shoulders, kettlebell on the floor in front of you.\n2. Hinge at hips to grab the bell, then hike it between your legs.\n3. Explosively snap your hips forward to swing the bell to chest height.\n4. Let the bell fall back between your legs and repeat.</string>
    <string name="ex_kb_swing_tech">Power comes from the hips, not the arms. Arms should act only as "ropes." Keep your back flat and your core braced at the top.</string>
    <string name="ex_kb_swing_mistakes">Using arms to lift the weight, squatting instead of hinging, and rounding the back.</string>

    <string name="ex_glute_bridge">Glute Bridge</string>
    <string name="ex_glute_bridge_desc">A focused exercise for isolating the glutes and strengthening the posterior chain.</string>
    <string name="ex_glute_bridge_steps">1. Lie on your back with knees bent and feet flat on the floor, hip-width apart.\n2. Drive through your heels to lift your hips toward the ceiling.\n3. Squeeze your glutes hard at the top of the movement.\n4. Slowly lower your hips back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_glute_bridge_tech">Keep your core engaged to avoid overarching your lower back. Your shins should be vertical at the top of the movement. Do not let your knees cave in.</string>
    <string name="ex_glute_bridge_mistakes">Overarching the lower back, lifting the heels off the floor, and not fully extending the hips.</string>

    <!-- New Exercises -->
    <string name="ex_scapular_pullups">Scapular Pull-ups</string>
    <string name="ex_scapular_pullups_desc">A subtle but powerful movement to strengthen the scapular stabilizers and improve shoulder health.</string>
    <string name="ex_scapular_pullups_steps">1. Hang from a pull-up bar with an overhand grip.\n2. Without bending your elbows, pull your shoulder blades down and together.\n3. Lift your body slightly using only your shoulders.\n4. Lower back to the starting dead-hang position with control.</string>
    <string name="ex_scapular_pullups_tech">Keep your arms completely straight throughout the movement. Focus on the squeeze between your shoulder blades. Avoid swinging your body.</string>
    <string name="ex_scapular_pullups_mistakes">Bending the elbows, using momentum to swing, and not reaching full extension at the bottom.</string>

    <string name="ex_snow_angels">Reverse Snow Angels</string>
    <string name="ex_snow_angels_desc">Strengthens the upper back and improves shoulder posture by engaging the traps and rhomboids.</string>
    <string name="ex_snow_angels_steps">1. Lie face down on the floor with arms at your sides, palms down.\n2. Lift your chest and arms slightly off the floor.\n3. Sweep your arms in a wide arc until they meet above your head.\n4. Reverse the movement back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_snow_angels_tech">Keep your forehead on or near the floor to maintain a neutral neck. Keep your arms as straight as possible. Move slowly and with control.</string>
    <string name="ex_snow_angels_mistakes">Arching the lower back excessively, lifting the head too high, and moving too fast.</string>

    <string name="ex_band_pullaparts">Band Pull-Aparts</string>
    <string name="ex_band_pullaparts_desc">Activates the rear deltoids and rhomboids for better shoulder alignment and stability.</string>
    <string name="ex_band_pullaparts_steps">1. Stand tall holding a resistance band in front of you at shoulder height.\n2. Keep your arms straight and pull the band apart toward your chest.\n3. Squeeze your shoulder blades together at the end of the movement.\n4. Slowly return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_band_pullaparts_tech">Keep your shoulders down and away from your ears. Ensure your core is tight and you are not arching your back. Focus on the horizontal pull.</string>
    <string name="ex_band_pullaparts_mistakes">Shrugging the shoulders, arching the back, and bending the elbows.</string>

    <string name="ex_thoracic_rotations">Thoracic Rotations</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_rotations_desc">Improves rotational mobility in the mid-back (thoracic spine), reducing stiffness and improving posture.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_rotations_steps">1. Start on all fours or in a half-kneeling position.\n2. Place one hand behind your head.\n3. Rotate your elbow toward the opposite knee, then rotate it toward the ceiling.\n4. Follow the movement with your eyes and repeat.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_rotations_tech">Keep your hips still and focus the rotation on your mid-back. Breathe out as you rotate toward the ceiling. Move smoothly without forcing the range.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_rotations_mistakes">Rotating through the hips, pulling on the neck with your hand, and rushing the rotation.</string>

    <string name="ex_cobra_stretch">Cobra Stretch</string>
    <string name="ex_cobra_stretch_desc">Opens up the chest and stretches the abdominal muscles while improving spinal extension.</string>
    <string name="ex_cobra_stretch_steps">1. Lie face down with hands placed under your shoulders.\n2. Press through your hands to lift your chest off the floor.\n3. Keep your hips on the ground and shoulders down.\n4. Look forward and hold the stretch while breathing.</string>
    <string name="ex_cobra_stretch_tech">Keep your shoulders away from your ears. Don\'t lock your elbows if it feels uncomfortable. Focus on a gentle curve throughout the spine.</string>
    <string name="ex_cobra_stretch_mistakes">Shrugging shoulders, lifting hips off the floor, and overextending the neck.</string>

    <string name="ex_childs_pose">Child\'s Pose</string>
    <string name="ex_childs_pose_desc">A resting pose that gently stretches the lower back, hips, and shoulders while promoting relaxation.</string>
    <string name="ex_childs_pose_steps">1. Kneel on the floor with big toes touching and sit on your heels.\n2. Fold forward and rest your forehead on the floor.\n3. Extend your arms forward or place them alongside your body.\n4. Breathe deeply and sink your hips toward your heels.</string>
    <string name="ex_childs_pose_tech">Breathe deeply into your back and ribcage. Relax your jaw and shoulders. If it\'s uncomfortable for the knees, widen the space between them.</string>
    <string name="ex_childs_pose_mistakes">Holding tension in the neck, holding breath, and lifting the hips too high from the heels.</string>

    <string name="ex_thoracic_extension">Thoracic Extension</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_extension_desc">Counters the "slumped" posture by extending the mid-back over a foam roller or chair.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_extension_steps">1. Sit or lie down with a foam roller or the edge of a chair behind your mid-back.\n2. Support your head with your hands.\n3. Gently lean back over the roller or chair, extending your upper spine.\n4. Return to the starting position and repeat at different levels of the mid-back.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_extension_tech">Focus on bending from the mid-back, not the lower back. Keep your ribs tucked in. Avoid pulling on your neck.</string>
    <string name="ex_thoracic_extension_mistakes">Arching the lower back, pulling the neck, and moving too quickly.</string>

    <string name="ex_hip_flexor_stretch">Hip Flexor Stretch</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_flexor_stretch_desc">Lengthens the tight muscles at the front of the hip, which can relieve lower back pain.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_flexor_stretch_steps">1. Kneel on one knee (half-kneeling position).\n2. Tuck your tailbone under and squeeze the glute of the back leg.\n3. Gently shift your weight forward until you feel a stretch in the front of your hip.\n4. Hold the position and breathe.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_flexor_stretch_tech">Squeeze the glute of the back leg to deepen the stretch safely. Keep your torso upright. Do not over-arch your lower back.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_flexor_stretch_mistakes">Arching the lower back, leaning too far forward without glute engagement, and holding breath.</string>

    <string name="ex_90_90_hips">90/90 Hips</string>
    <string name="ex_90_90_hips_desc">A versatile movement for improving internal and external hip rotation and overall hip mobility.</string>
    <string name="ex_90_90_hips_steps">1. Sit on the floor with your front leg at a 90-degree angle and back leg also at 90 degrees.\n2. Keep your torso upright and square to your front leg.\n3. Lean forward slightly over the front leg to stretch the glute.\n4. Rotate your torso toward the back leg to work on internal rotation.</string>
    <string name="ex_90_90_hips_tech">Try to keep your torso as upright as possible throughout the movement. Breathe into the tight areas of the hips. Use your hands for support if needed.</string>
    <string name="ex_90_90_hips_mistakes">Rounding the back, rushing the movement, and ignoring sharp pain.</string>

    <string name="ex_hamstring_stretch">Hamstring Stretch</string>
    <string name="ex_hamstring_stretch_desc">Relieves tension in the back of the legs and can help improve overall mobility.</string>
    <string name="ex_hamstring_stretch_steps">1. Stand or sit with one leg extended in front of you.\n2. Keep your back straight and hinge forward at the hips.\n3. Reach toward your toes until you feel a gentle stretch.\n4. Hold and breathe deeply.</string>
    <string name="ex_hamstring_stretch_tech">Keep a slight bend in the knee to protect the joint. Focus on hinging at the hips rather than rounding the back. Keep your toes pointed up.</string>
    <string name="ex_hamstring_stretch_mistakes">Rounding the back, locking the knee, and bouncing in the stretch.</string>

    <string name="ex_neck_circles">Neck Circles</string>
    <string name="ex_neck_circles_desc">Gently warms up the neck muscles and improves cervical mobility.</string>
    <string name="ex_neck_circles_steps">1. Drop your chin to your chest.\n2. Slowly rotate your head in a full circle.\n3. Move with control and avoid any sharp pain.\n4. Switch directions after several rotations.</string>
    <string name="ex_neck_circles_tech">Move slowly and breathe. Do not force the range of motion. Keep your shoulders relaxed.</string>
    <string name="ex_neck_circles_mistakes">Moving too fast, shrugging shoulders, and forcing through pain.</string>

    <string name="ex_arm_circles">Arm Circles</string>
    <string name="ex_arm_circles_desc">Increases blood flow and mobility in the shoulder joints.</string>
    <string name="ex_arm_circles_steps">1. Stand with arms extended out to the sides at shoulder height.\n2. Make small circles with your arms, gradually increasing the size.\n3. Perform circles in both forward and backward directions.\n4. Keep your core engaged and torso still.</string>
    <string name="ex_arm_circles_tech">Keep your arms straight. Control the movement from the shoulders. Don\'t let your torso swing.</string>
    <string name="ex_arm_circles_mistakes">Bending elbows, swinging the torso, and moving too quickly.</string>

    <string name="ex_hip_circles">Hip Circles</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_circles_desc">Warms up the hip joints and lower back muscles.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_circles_steps">1. Stand with feet shoulder-width apart and hands on your hips.\n2. Rotate your hips in a large circular motion.\n3. Imagine you are using your hips to draw a circle on the floor.\n4. Switch directions after several rotations.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_circles_tech">Keep your feet flat on the floor. Move through a full, comfortable range of motion. Breathe naturally.</string>
    <string name="ex_hip_circles_mistakes">Moving too fast, keeping hips too stiff, and lifting feet.</string>

    <string name="ex_leg_swings">Leg Swings</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_swings_desc">A dynamic stretch for the hips, hamstrings, and glutes.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_swings_steps">1. Stand next to a wall or support for balance.\n2. Swing one leg forward and backward in a controlled manner.\n3. Gradually increase the height of the swing as you warm up.\n4. Switch legs and repeat.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_swings_tech">Keep your torso upright; don\'t lean forward or back. Control the swing with your muscles, don\'t just use momentum. Keep your core engaged.</string>
    <string name="ex_leg_swings_mistakes">Leaning the torso, using excessive momentum, and locking the standing leg knee.</string>

    <string name="ex_jumping_jacks">Jumping Jacks</string>
    <string name="ex_jumping_jacks_desc">A classic full-body warm-up that increases heart rate and improves coordination.</string>
    <string name="ex_jumping_jacks_steps">1. Stand with feet together and arms at your sides.\n2. Jump up, spreading your legs and swinging arms above your head.\n3. Jump again to return to the starting position.\n4. Maintain a steady rhythm.</string>
    <string name="ex_jumping_jacks_tech">Land softly on the balls of your feet. Keep a slight bend in your knees. Move your arms in a full range of motion.</string>
    <string name="ex_jumping_jacks_mistakes">Landing flat-footed, keeping arms stiff, and holding breath.</string>

    <string name="ex_hang">Active Hang</string>
    <string name="ex_hang_desc">A fundamental grip and shoulder health exercise that decompresses the spine.</string>
    <string name="ex_hang_steps">1. Grab a pull-up bar with an overhand grip.\n2. Let your body hang freely with arms fully extended.\n3. Engage your shoulders by pulling them down away from your ears (active hang).\n4. Hold the position for the required time.</string>
    <string name="ex_hang_tech">Keep your core slightly engaged to avoid excessive arching. Maintain an "active" shoulder position. Breathe steadily throughout the hold.</string>
    <string name="ex_hang_mistakes">Dead hanging (relaxing shoulders completely), holding breath, and swinging.</string>

    <string name="ex_face_pull">Face Pull</string>
    <string name="ex_face_pull_desc">An excellent exercise for rear deltoid development and improving shoulder posture.</string>
    <string name="ex_face_pull_steps">1. Attach a rope or band at eye level.\n2. Pull the handles toward your face, pulling the ends apart.\n3. Squeeze your shoulder blades together at the end of the movement.\n4. Slowly return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_face_pull_tech">Focus on pulling with your elbows and rotating your hands back. Keep your chest up. Do not use momentum to pull the weight.</string>
    <string name="ex_face_pull_mistakes">Using too much weight, pulling to the chest instead of the face, and shrugging shoulders.</string>
    <string name="ex_superman">Superman</string>
    <string name="ex_superman_desc">A movement designed to strengthen the lower back and improve posture by engaging the entire posterior chain.</string>
    <string name="ex_superman_steps">1. Lie face down on the floor with arms extended overhead.\n2. Simultaneously lift your arms, chest, and legs off the ground.\n3. Hold the "flying" position for 2-3 seconds.\n4. Slowly lower back down to the floor.</string>
    <string name="ex_superman_tech">Keep your neck neutral by looking at the floor. Focus on the squeeze in your lower back and glutes. Move with control rather than using momentum.</string>
    <string name="ex_superman_mistakes">Looking up too high, jerky movements, and holding breath.</string>

    <string name="ex_wall_slides">Wall Slides</string>
    <string name="ex_wall_slides_desc">An excellent drill for improving shoulder mobility and upper back posture.</string>
    <string name="ex_wall_slides_steps">1. Stand with your back against a wall, feet slightly forward.\n2. Place your arms against the wall in a "W" shape (elbows and wrists touching the wall).\n3. Slowly slide your arms up into a "Y" shape without losing contact with the wall.\n4. Slide back down to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex_wall_slides_tech">Keep your lower back pressed into the wall. If your wrists or elbows lift off, only go as high as you can maintain contact. Quality over quantity.</string>
    <string name="ex_wall_slides_mistakes">Arching the lower back, allowing elbows/wrists to lift off the wall, and shrugging shoulders.</string>

    <string name="ex_pike_pushups">Pike Pushups</string>
    <string name="ex_pike_pushups_desc">An advanced push-up variation that shifts the focus toward the shoulders and upper chest.</string>
    <string name="ex_pike_pushups_steps">1. Start in a downward dog position with hips high in the air.\n2. Lower the top of your head toward the floor between your hands.\n3. Push back up until your arms are fully extended.\n4. Keep your legs as straight as possible throughout.</string>
    <string name="ex_pike_pushups_tech">Form a tripod with your head and hands at the bottom of the movement. Tuck your elbows slightly inward. The more vertical your torso, the harder the exercise.</string>
    <string name="ex_pike_pushups_mistakes">Flaring elbows, letting hips sag, and lowering the head behind the hands rather than forward.</string>

    <string name="ex_horse_stance">Horse Stance</string>
    <string name="ex_horse_stance_desc">A traditional isometric hold that builds incredible leg strength and hip mobility.</string>
    <string name="ex_horse_stance_steps">1. Stand with feet double shoulder-width apart, toes pointed slightly outward.\n2. Sink your hips down until thighs are parallel to the floor.\n3. Keep your back straight and hands in front or on your hips.\n4. Hold the position for the required time while breathing deeply.</string>
    <string name="ex_horse_stance_tech">Tuck your pelvis slightly to avoid overarching the lower back. Distribute weight evenly across the entire foot. Focus on a steady, calm breath.</string>
    <string name="ex_horse_stance_mistakes">Letting the knees collapse inward, rounding the back, and not sinking deep enough.</string>
    <string name="ex_deep_squat">Deep Squat Hold</string>
    <string name="ex_deep_squat_desc">A fundamental movement for hip, knee, and ankle mobility.</string>
    <string name="ex_deep_squat_steps">1. Stand with feet shoulder-width apart.\n2. Lower your hips as deep as possible while keeping heels on the ground.\n3. Use your elbows to gently push your knees outward.\n4. Maintain an upright chest and hold the position.</string>
    <string name="ex_deep_squat_tech">Keep your heels flat on the floor. If they lift, widen your stance. Keep your chest up and breathe deeply into the belly.</string>
    <string name="ex_deep_squat_mistakes">Lifting heels, rounding the back excessively, and caving knees inward.</string>

    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="sets">Sets</string>
    <string name="reps">Reps</string>
    <string name="seconds_format">%1$ds</string>
    <string name="sets_reps_format">%1$d × %2$d</string>
    <string name="chart_label">Workouts per week</string>
    <string name="timer_format">%1$02d:%2$02d</string>

    <string name="wt_strength_a">Strength A</string>
    <string name="wt_strength_b">Strength B</string>
    <string name="wt_mobility">Mobility</string>
    <string name="wt_functional">Functional</string>
    <string name="wt_rest">Rest</string>
</resources>
